9099725087



CARLOS NORIEGA

PROFILE

I'm an experienced creative professional with 10 years of experience in different facets of digital content. I'm the owner of my own content creation company called Noriega Productions where I create digital content and social media campaigns for the advertising and marketing of my clients. Committed to utilizing my skills to further the mission of anyone I work with. I've been offering remote editing and post finishing services and I take a highly collaborative approach to helping my clients.

Skills

- Communication Skills
- Adobe After Effects CC
- Leadership and Teamwork
- Fast Learner
- Final Cut Pro X

carlos noriega 9099725087

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Premiere Pro
HTML/CSS/JavaScript

O Python O Adobe Illustrator

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Noriega Productions, Rancho Cucamonga

January 2012 — Present

- Film Post Production Services
- Video Editor
- Motion Graphics Artist
- Photography
- Streaming Media / Webcasting / Live Streaming Services
- Graphic Designers / Graphic Design

Lead Creative at Apple, Rancho Cucamonga

January 2010 - January 2017

- Promote and model the benefits of Apple's ecosystem to customers, our internal team, and the community at large
- Deep understanding of the creative community, and you'll speak from your own experiences and stories, so that others understand the full potential of our products and services
- Foster a learning environment for our customers in the store by connecting their interests to the Apple ecosystem
- Retail expert in music, photography, art, gaming, and more
- Facilitating learning around these topics for internal and external customers, you help everyone understand the possibilities created by Apple technology
- Delivered engaging workshops with strong customer participation

EDUCATION

Full Stack Dev, Codecademy

January 2020 — January 2022

- Proficient understanding of web markup, including HTML5 and CSS
- Data base set up with node npm and mongo db
- Proficient understanding of client-side scripting and JavaScript frameworks.

carlos noriega		9099725087
LINKS	My Linkedin profile	